<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="99">
    <author>Temmmych</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
	
    <title>
        <en>Production Watcher</en>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[This mod adds a notification system for production facilities.

Alerts are triggered in the following cases:
- Input materials drop below 5% or run out.
- Output storage exceeds 95% or becomes full (with direct selling disabled).

Each production can send only one active notification for raw materials and one for output storage to avoid spam. Priority is always given to more critical alerts.
This helps prevent production downtime or product loss.

Default keys:
- Hide/Show all notifications: Shift+Q
- Cursor Hide/Show: MMB]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Diese Mod fügt ein Benachrichtigungssystem für Produktionsgebäude hinzu.

Benachrichtigungen werden in folgenden Fällen ausgelöst:
-Rohstoffe fallen unter 5% oder gehen aus.
-Das Lager ist zu mehr als 95% gefüllt oder vollständig voll (bei deaktiviertem Direktverkauf).

Jede Produktion kann nur eine aktive Benachrichtigung für Rohstoffe und eine für das Lager senden, um Spam zu vermeiden. Kritische Meldungen haben immer Priorität.
So lassen sich Produktionsstopps oder Produktverluste vermeiden.

Standardtasten:
- Alle Benachrichtigungen ein-/ausblenden: Shift+Q
- Cursor Ausblenden/Einblenden: MMB]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Ce mod ajoute un système de notifications pour les sites de production.

Des alertes sont déclenchées dans les cas suivants :
- Les matières premières passent sous 5% ou sont épuisées.
- Le stock de produits dépasse 95% ou est plein (vente directe désactivée).

Chaque production ne peut envoyer qu’une seule notification active pour les matières premières et une pour le stockage afin d’éviter le spam.
Les alertes les plus critiques sont prioritaires. Cela permet d’éviter les arrêts de production ou la perte de produits.

Touches par défaut:
- Afficher/Masquer toutes les notifications: Shift+Q
- Curseur Masquer/Afficher: MMB]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[Este mod añade un sistema de notificaciones para las instalaciones de producción.

Las alertas se activan en los siguientes casos:
- Los insumos bajan del 5% o se agotan.
- El almacén de productos supera el 95% o está lleno (con venta directa desactivada).

Cada instalación puede enviar solo una notificación activa por materias primas y una por almacenamiento para evitar spam.
Siempre se da prioridad a los avisos más críticos. Ayuda a evitar paros de producción o pérdida de productos.

Teclas predeterminadas:
- Mostrar/Ocultar todas las notificaciones: Shift+Q
- Ocultar/Mostrar el Cursor: MMB]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Этот мод добавляет систему уведомлений для производственных объектов.

Оповещения срабатывают в следующих случаях:
- Входные материалы падают ниже 5% или заканчиваются.
- Выходное хранилище достигает более 95% или заполняется (при отключенных прямых продажах).

Каждое производство может отправить только одно активное оповещение по сырью и одно по складу, чтобы избежать спама. Приоритет всегда отдаётся более критичным сообщениям.
Это помогает не упустить важные моменты в работе производств и избежать простоя или потери продукции.

Клавиши по умолчанию:
- Скрыть/Показать все уведомления: Shift+Q
- Скрыть/Показать курсор: MMB]]></ru>
        <it><![CDATA[Questa mod aggiunge un sistema di notifiche per gli impianti di produzione.

Le notifiche si attivano nei seguenti casi:
- Le scorte scendono sotto il 5% o si esauriscono.
- Il magazzino supera il 95% o è pieno (con vendita diretta disattivata).

Ogni produzione può inviare solo una notifica attiva per le materie prime e una per lo stoccaggio, per evitare spam.
La priorità viene sempre data agli avvisi più critici. Aiuta a evitare interruzioni della produzione o perdite di prodotto.

Tasti predefiniti:
- Mostra/Nascondi tutte le notifiche: Shift+Q
- Nascondi/Mostra il Cursore: MMB]]></it>
        <pl><![CDATA[Mod dodaje system powiadomień dla zakładów produkcyjnych.

Powiadomienia pojawiają się w następujących przypadkach:
- Surowce spadają poniżej 5% lub się kończą.
- Magazyn przekracza 95% pojemności lub jest pełny (przy wyłączonej sprzedaży bezpośredniej).

Każda produkcja może wysłać tylko jedno aktywne powiadomienie o surowcach i jedno o magazynie, aby uniknąć spamu.
Priorytet mają zawsze ważniejsze alerty. Pomaga to uniknąć przestojów i strat produkcyjnych.

Domyślne klawisze:
- Pokaż/Ukryj wszystkie powiadomienia: Shift+Q
- Ukryj/Pokaż Kursor: MMB]]></pl>
    </description>

    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <iconFilename>icon_production_watcher.dds</iconFilename>

    <actions>
		<action name="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_INPUT_ACTION_KEY" />
        <action name="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_CURSOR_ACTION_KEY" />
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_INPUT_ACTION_KEY">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_q" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_CURSOR_ACTION_KEY">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_MIDDLE" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="3" />
		</actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <l10n>
        <text name="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_INPUT_ACTION_KEY">
            <en>PW: Hide/Show</en>
            <de>PW: Ausblenden/Einblenden</de>
            <fr>PW: Masquer/Afficher</fr>
            <es>PW: Ocultar/Mostrar</es>
            <ru>PW: Скрыть/Показать</ru>
            <it>PW: Nascondi/Mostra</it>
            <pl>PW: Ukryj/Pokaż</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="input_PRODUCTIONWATCHER_INPUT_ACTION_KEY">
            <en>Hide/Show notifications</en>
            <de>Benachrichtigungen ausblenden/einblenden</de>
            <fr>Masquer/Afficher les notifications</fr>
            <es>Ocultar/Mostrar notificaciones</es>
            <ru>Скрыть/Показать уведомления</ru>
            <it>Nascondi/Mostra notifiche</it>
            <pl>Ukryj/Pokaż powiadomienia</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="PRODUCTIONWATCHER_CURSOR_ACTION_KEY">
            <en>PW: Cursor Hide/Show</en>
            <de>PW: Cursor Ausblenden/Einblenden</de>
            <fr>PW: Curseur Masquer/Afficher</fr>
            <es>PW: Ocultar/Mostrar el Cursor</es>
            <ru>PW: Скрыть/Показать курсор</ru>
            <it>PW: Nascondi/Mostra il Cursore</it>
            <pl>PW: Ukryj/Pokaż Kursor</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="input_PRODUCTIONWATCHER_CURSOR_ACTION_KEY">
            <en>Cursor Hide/Show</en>
            <de>Cursor Ausblenden/Einblenden</de>
            <fr>Curseur Masquer/Afficher</fr>
            <es>Ocultar/Mostrar el Cursor</es>
            <ru>Скрыть/Показать курсор</ru>
            <it>Nascondi/Mostra il Cursore</it>
            <pl>Ukryj/Pokaż Kursor</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="message_matreials_5">
            <en>materials &lt; 5%</en>
            <de>material &lt; 5%</de>
            <fr>matériaux &lt; 5%</fr>
            <es>materiales &lt; 5%</es>
            <ru>материлов &lt; 5%</ru>
            <it>materiali &lt; 5%</it>
            <pl>materiałów &lt; 5%</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="message_matreials_empty">
            <en>no materials</en>
            <de>kein Material</de>
            <fr>pas de matériau</fr>
            <es>sin material</es>
            <ru>нет материлов</ru>
            <it>nessun materiale</it>
            <pl>brak materiałów</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="message_stock_95">
            <en>in stock &gt; 95%</en>
            <de>lager &gt; 95%</de>
            <fr>en stock &gt; 95%</fr>
            <es>en stock &gt; 95%</es>
            <ru>на складе &gt; 95%</ru>
            <it>in magazzino &gt; 95%</it>
            <pl>w magazynie &gt; 95%</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="message_stock_full">
            <en>warehouse full</en>
            <de>lager voll</de>
            <fr>stock plein</fr>
            <es>almacén lleno</es>
            <ru>склад полный</ru>
            <it>magazzino pien</it>
            <pl>magazyn pełny</pl>
        </text>
    </l10n>
	
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/MessageWindow.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/ProductionWatcher.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>